Today, before the sun appears, I
bathe, get ready, lovingly
touch the feet of the elders of the family,
seek their blessings, and leave with my very intelligent platoon for
my life. Sorry, Wagner.
But where is Noida?
Because I have received an invitation from the department.
Yes, I have already missed two of my events before this,
and I don't want to
miss this one. So,
what's the point of quenching my thirst with the car? This is
Aunt Tuntun's new startup. Finally, we
enter Noida and have been invited to a very appropriate place.
Due to limited space,
only I am inside the event and we are told everything is fine. It feels
good,
so I bend my wrists and, after receiving my gift
bag, I roll my eyes. I do
n't recognize a single person here
except this one. So that they don't feel that my invitation was a waste, I
come to the point, have tea and
snacks. Your focus is only on food, right? Does
that mean you are also focused on food? Yes, that's
exactly what you want, brother. My focus is also on
food. Then what? Eat, drink, enjoy,
how will Thanos play a trick now?  You don't have to be so serious,
I create beauty content, so let it be, I am
joking, these two are the
hosts of this event, whom I did
not know at all before today, what a thing,
hey beautiful, the rest of the story in the next part.